http://www.kalfusnachman.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyWe recognize that you may be concerned about our use and disclosure of your personal information. Your privacy is very important to us, and the following will inform you of the information that we, Kalfus & Nachman PC, may collect from you, and how it is used. By using our website, www.kalfusnachman.com, you are accepting the practices described in this policy.
Information CollectionWe may collect non-personal information, such as a domain name and IP Address. The domain name and IP address reveals nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We may also collect information about the type of Internet browser you are using, operating system, what brought you to our Website, as well as which of our Web pages you have accessed.Additionally, if you communicate with us regarding our Website or our services, we will collect any information that you provide to us in any such communication.We may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Information UseWe use the collected information primarily for our own internal purposes, such as providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving our services and Website, fulfilling requests for information, and providing customer support.
ConsentBy using this Website, you consent to the collection and use of information as specified above. If we make changes to our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page. Please review this page frequently to remain up-to-date with the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. You must review the new Privacy Policy carefully to make sure you understand our practices and procedures.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at
(855) 880-8163 or via mail Attn: Privacy Officer, 749 J Clyde Morris Blvd, Suite B, Newport News, VA 23601.
You Will Pay No Fees Unless We Win Your Case
We Have Recovered Millions of Dollars for Our Clients
Our Attorneys Are Well-Equipped to Fight Insurance Companies
We Have Successfully Handled Thousands of Cases Since 1979
We are a Full-Service Firm with Multiple Locations
Se Habla Español
First Name
Please enter your first name.
Last Name
Please enter your last name.
Phone
Please enter your phone number.
This isn't a valid phone number.
Email
Please enter your email address.
This isn't a valid email address.
Yes, I am a potential new client
No, I'm a current existing client
I'm neither.
Are you a new client?
Please make a selection.
Message
Please enter a message.
Send Information
